Some secrets should stay buried
Inheritance is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Vaughn Stein.
The patriarch of a wealthy and powerful family suddenly passes away, leaving his wife and daughter
with a shocking secret inheritance that threatens to unravel and destroy their lives.
Lauren Monroe, played by Lily Collins.
Morgan Warner, played by Simon Pegg.
Catherine Monroe, played by Connie Nielsen.
William Monroe, played by Chace Crawford.
Archer Monroe, played by Patrick Warburton.
Scott, played by Marque Richardson.
Inheritance is a 2020 American thriller film directed by
Vaughn Stein and written by Matthew Kennedy.
The film stars Lily Collins, Simon Pegg, Connie Nielsen,
Chace Crawford and Patrick Warburton.
Inheritance was released on May 22, 2020, by Vertical Entertainment.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of daughter, father,
patriarchy, family secrets, buried memories.
The tone is intense and mind_bending and dark.